Guide to the Rupert G. Miller Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Rupert G. Miller papers
1949-1986
SC0742
Miller, Rupert G.
37 Linear feet (68 boxes)
The papers pertain to Miller's professional career as researcher, professor, and author, with some materials from his days as a student. Includes drafts of papers, lectures and books; research notes and files; conference materials and organizational files; class files; minutes, reports, and other records pertaining to administrative duties at Stanford; and video tapes of his Stanford lectures (1982).
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
This collection was given to the Stanford University Archives by the estate of Rupert G. Miller in 2003.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Rupert Miller taught at Stanford University from 1959 until his death in 1986; he held a joint appointment between the Department of Statistics and the School of Medicine (Division of Biostatistics), where he served as a consultant to researchers on data analysis. He was chair of the statistics department from 1969-1972 and received one of the first dean's awards for superior teaching in 1977.
Miller earned his B.A. in mathematics at Princeton in 1954 and his doctorate in statistics at Stanford in 1958. He taught at Johns Hopkins in 1963-1964, was a Guggenheim fellow in 1972-1973, and served as editor of the Annals of Statistics. His books include Survival Analysis, Simultaneous Statistical Inference, and Beyond ANOVA, Basics of Applied Statistics.
Description of the Collection
The papers pertain to Miller's professional career as researcher, professor, and author, with some materials from his days as a student. The collection includes class files containing lecture notes, syllabi, exams, and other materials; departmental files containing minutes, memoranda, reports, and other records; grant files, conference papers, research reports, and other professional records; drafts of articles and books, as well as reprints of his journal articles; and videotapes of his lectures from Statistics 116, 1982. The following subject groupings have been identified: Academic Career, Conferences and Organizations, Manuscripts and Reports, Side Projects and Reviews, Reprints, and Audio Visual Materials.
Access Terms
Miller, Rupert G.; Stanford University. Department of Statistics. Faculty.; Mathematical statistics.; Medical statistics; Statistics--Study and teaching.
Collection Contents
- Unbalanced Jacknife, 1973-83 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Weighted Jacknife, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Jacknife review, 1973-80 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Two sample sequential rank test, 1973-79 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Reed-Meunch = Spearman-Karber, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Functional Central Limit Theorem for U-Statistics, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Sequential Rank Tests-One Sample Case, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Simultaneous Discrimination Intervals, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 2 x 2 Tables (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Sequential Signed Rank (Second Revision), 1966-1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Sequential Signed-Rank (Revised), 1969-1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Sequential Signed-Rank, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Sequential Signed Rank Old or Incorrect, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Applied Probability (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Applied Probability Handouts (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Jackknife Talk (Variances), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Jackknife on Variances, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Calibration Problem, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Bailey Stochastic Processes, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Feller's Limit Theorem (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Takacs Review: Queues, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Tukey Jackknife (New) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Tukey Jackknife (Old) (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Trustworthy Jackknife, 1964-1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Stationarity Equations Talk (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Foster Theorems (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Stationarity Equations Talk (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Simultaneous Tolerance Intervals, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Simultaneous Tolerance Extra (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Renewal Theorem (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Multivariate Occupation Times (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Storage Processes, 1963-1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Continuous Time Storage Processes (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Takacs Limit Distributions III (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Takacs Limit Distributions III (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Takacs Limit Distributions I, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Persistence (1 of 2), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Persistence (2 of 2), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Counting Times (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Early Failures - Revised (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Early Failures, 1976-1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Priority Queues (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Priority Queues (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Bulk Queues (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Bulk Queues (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Sandia Report (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Scheffe 2-dim projections, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Regression Jackknife in Groups (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Olkin's "abs. value (mu1-mu0) = abs. value (mu2-mu0)" Problem, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- SCI Lipchitz Condition (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Survival Analyis - Conditional, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Censored CDFs (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Data Functions (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Uniform width calibration intervals (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Three Sequential Boundaries (Box 5, Folder 15)
- J. Arveson - Jackknife = MLE (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Smoothing (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Pitman-Bahadur-Invariance (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Nonlinear Estimation (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Jackknife: Functional Relation (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Chebyshev t (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Jackknife in Balanced Bioassay (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Successive Prediction (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Stationarity Equations in Branching Processes (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Prediction v. Discrimination (Box 6, Folder 2)
- C. Weaver - Separation Problems (Box 6, Folder 3)
- A.S. Ratio Limits (crossed-out) (Box 6, Folder 4)
- L. Parent: Nonparametric Sequential (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Takacs Limit Distributions II (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Games of Survival (Box 6, Folder 7)
- M.L. Jackknife, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- B. Efron - Max{xi}/Exi (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Random Walk On Circle (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Busy Period G/M/1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Busy Period GI/M/1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Optimum Experimental Designs (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Vn (Box 6, Folder 14)
- MLE on Circle and Sphere (Box 6, Folder 15)
- (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Ignitron Tubes (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Cascade Processes (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Interpretation of yQ=0; Q explosive (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Uniqueness of Q process (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Discussion - Hubev's Paper, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Heart Transplant Data - Dates, all patients, Feb 80, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Data (Herzberg), 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Gaver-Miller - Jackknife KME, 1978-1983 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- What price Kaplan-Meier?, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Maximally Selected X^2, 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Multiple Comparisons, 1979-1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Halpern/Miller II - Censored Regression Estimators, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Meredith Miller, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Meredith Miller II, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Biostatistic Casebook III, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Casebook III, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Robust Estimators in Quantal Bioassay (1 of 2), 1979-1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Robust Estimators in Quantal Bioassay (2 of 2), 1979-1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Biostatistics Casebook II, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Jackknife: Survey and Applications, 1978-1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Advances in Multiple Comparisons, 1976-1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Combing 2x2 Contingency Tables, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Jackknife on Kaplan-Meier, 1976-1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Reaven and Miller: Diabetes, 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Censored Least Squares (1st, 2nd, 3rd Revisions) (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Survival Analysis - 2nd Revision (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Survival Analysis - Regression Write-up and Revision (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Survival Analysis - Regression, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- SSI: Springer, 1979-1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Simultaneous Statistical Inference (SSI) Manuscript, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- SSI: Editing and Typesetting, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Illustrations, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Copy 2: Extra Sheets, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Chapter IV: Copy 2, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Index: Copy 2, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Chapter III: Copy 2, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Bibliography: Copy 2, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Chapter II: Copy 2, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Appendices A,B: Copy 2, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Chapter I: Copy 2, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Chapter VI: Copy 2, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Preface, Table of Contents, Acknowledgements, Dedication, Special Symbols: Copy 2, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Index, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Appendix B, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Appendix A, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Chapter V, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Chapter VI, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Chapter III, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Chapter II, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Chapter I, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- SSI: Bibliography, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- SSI: Appendix B, Tables, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- SSI: Appendix A, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Chapter VI, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Chapter V, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Chapter IV: pp 101-, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Chapter IV: pp 1-100, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Chapter IV, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- SSI: Chapter III, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Chapter II: Copy, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Chapter II pp. 130-232, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Chapter II pp. 1-129, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Chapter II (Typed Manuscript), 1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- SSI: Chapter II, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Chapter I (Typed Manuscript), 1966 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- SSI: Chapter I, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- SSI: Optimality (Chapter I), 1966 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Preface, Table of Contents, Acknowledgements, etc., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Computations: SSI, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Simultaneous Statistical Inference, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Layard Comments, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Tukey Comments, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Currey Comments, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- "Stanford Statistics", 1985 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Miscellaneous Correpondence, 1983-1986 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Simultaneous Statistical Inference Correspondence, 1964-1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- SSI: Wilby, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- SSI: McGraw-Hill, 1964-1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- McGraw-Hill Market Survey, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Complimentary Copies, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Copywright Permissions, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- McGraw-Hill Royalties, 1966-1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- SSI: Book Reviews, 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Xerox University Microfilms, 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- SSI: Book Orders (University Microfilms), 1975-1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- SSI Revisions, 1967-1970 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Final Manuscirpt: Chapter I, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Final Manuscirpt: Chapter II, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Final Manuscirpt: Chapter III, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Final Manuscirpt: Chapter IV, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Final Manuscirpt: Chapter V, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Final Manuscirpt: Chapter VI, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Final Manuscirpt: Appendix B, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Statistics 233 A, B: Applied Statistics (lectures by Miller; notes by Carol Link), 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Statistics 233 C: Applied Statistics (lectures by Persi Diaconis; notes by Andre Cabannes), 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Lectures on Multiple Comparisons, FDA, March 1979 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Biostatistics casebook: typescripts, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Biostatistics casebook: author's questionnaire (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Biostatistics casebook: contract and correspondence, 1978-83 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Biostatistics casebook: correspondence, authors and Wiley (publisher), 1980-82 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Statistics 233C Notebook I (Spring Quarter), 1985 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Statistics 233C Notebook II (Spring Quarter), 1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Statistics 233C: Survival Analysis Notebook I (Spring Quarter), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Statistics 233C: Survival Analysis Notebook II (Spring Quarter), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Survival Analysis - Original Notes, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Survival Analysis - Corrections, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Survival Analysis - Final Typing, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Survival Analysis, 1980-1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Beyond Anova: Introduction (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter I, One Sample (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter II, Two Samples (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter III, One-Way Classification (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Beyond Anova: Correspondence, 1971-1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Beyond Anova: Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Beyond Anova: Preface, etc., 1984 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Beyond Anova: Comments, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Beyond Anova: Preface (revised), 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter I, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter I (revised), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter II, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter II (revised), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter III, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter III (revised), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter IV, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter V, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter VI, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter VII, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter VIII, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Beyond Anova: Exercises, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Beyond Anova: References, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Beyond Anova: Preface (Typed Sheets), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Beyond Anova: References (Typed Sheets), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter I (Typed Sheets), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter II (Typed Sheets), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter III (Typed Sheets), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Beyond Anova: Chapter VIII (Typed Sheets), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- J. Pool: ACD vs. ADEN (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Creger: Brad Kininogen, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Creger-Anderson: Platelets at Altitude (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Northway: Rat Lung Slices (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Baldauf/Swenson: Muscle Grade (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Pass: Phototherapy of Newborns, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Stevens/Raffin: Covariability, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Butcher: Lymphocyte Adherence, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Reaven: I/G Ratios, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Swenson: Renal Failure, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Kalman: Cumulative Repression (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Mason: Insulin and Anesthetics, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Pool: Inhibitor Panel, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- K. Gardner: Pailla Excision (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Reaven: Leucine I (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Marlon: Cardiac Output (Jackknife Review) (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Stocker: Bacteria Clearance (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Kaplan: Purine Starvation (Box 21, Folder 3)
- L. Morrell: Reaction Times (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Olefsky: Tirglycerides (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Gabourel: Protein and DNA Synthesis (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Gardner: Vasopressin (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Gregory: Severe Viral Hepatitis (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Embury, et. al.: ACL Remission (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Jan Howard: Death Rates (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Anova: Preface, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Anova: Chapter 1, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Anova: Chapter 2, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Anova: Chapter 3, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Anova: Chapter 4, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Anova: Chapter 5, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Anova: Chapter 6, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Anova: Chapter 7, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Anova: Author Index, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Anova: Subject Index, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Anova: Complete Manuscript (Chapters 1-5), 1984 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Anova: Complete Manuscript (Chapters 3-7), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Chapter 1: One Sample (Corrected Copy), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Chapter 2: Two Samples (Corrected Copy), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Chapter 3: One-Way Classifications (Corrected Copy), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Chapter 4: Two-Way Classifications (Corrected Copy), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Chapter 5: Regression (Corrected Copy), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Chapter 6: Ratios (Corrected Copy), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- References (Edits) (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Wylbur: User's Guide, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Chapter 7: Variances (Corrected Copy), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 47)
- Exercises (Corrected Copy), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 48)
- References (Corrected Copy), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 49)
- Beyond Anova: Early Versions (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 50)
- Beyond Anova: Early Versions (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 51)
- Chapters 1 (Edits) (Box 22, Folder 52)
- Chapter 2 (Edits) (Box 22, Folder 53)
- Chapter 3 (Edits) (Box 22, Folder 54)
- Chapter 4 (Edits) (Box 22, Folder 55)
- Chapter 5 (Edits) (Box 22, Folder 56)
- Chapter 6 (Edits) (Box 22, Folder 57)
- Author Index Cards (Brown Box) (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Subject Index Cards (Gray Box) (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Faculty Benefits, 1966-1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Atomic Energy Commission Clearance, 1954-1964 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- National Register of Scientific Personnel, 1960-1962 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Professional Societies, 1960-1984 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- References, 1957-1961 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Results and Problems (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Manuscripts and Talks II, 1963-1985 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Research Proposal Recommendations, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Referee Reports, 1980-1985 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Stanford Ph.D's in Statistics, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- ASA Building Fund, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Job Opportunities, 1976-1985 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Maps (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Student Recommendations, 1976-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Faculty Recommendations I, 1982-1986 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous I, 1964-1973 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous II, 1979-1985 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Jobs, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Graduate Schools, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- 49ers, 1960-1962 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Stanford University, 1954-1958 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Research Problems (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Oral Exams, 1963-1972 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, Manuscripts, and Talks, 1958-1963 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Referee II, 1968-1979 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Newspapers, 1977-1981 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Student Evaluation of Teaching, 1976-1983 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Faculty Recommendations II, 1970-1981 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Examinations (Statistics), 1956-1983 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Examinations (Probability), 1958-1965 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Homework Problems, 1960-1980 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Statistics 60 (Exams, Homework, Handouts), 1978 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Statistics 60 - 1983 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Statistics 60 - Autumn, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Statistics 116 -1982 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Statistics 116 (Homework and Exams), 1982 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Statistics 217-21 (Homework, Exams, Syllabi), 1975-1982 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Statistics 217-218, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Statistics 233C: Survival Analysis (Spring Quarter, 1985) (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Applied Probability Handouts (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Qualifying Exams (1 of 2), 1963-1980 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Qualifying Exams (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Oral Exam Committees, 1973-1985 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Mathematics 105, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Mathematics 106, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Mathematics 203A (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Mathematics 219, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Mathematics 303, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Mathematics 304, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Mathematics 306, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Mathematics 308, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Mathematics 309, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Mathematics 309 (Lab), 1954 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Mathematics 310 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Mathematics 313, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Mathematics 315, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Mathematics 317, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Mathematics 319, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Mathematics 320 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Junior Department Work, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Senior Department Work, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Senior Thesis - Rough Draft, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Game Theory - Class Notes, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Extra Homework Copies (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Statistics Department (Executive Head) I, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Faculty Replacements for 1969-1979, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Meetings with Staff, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Student Support, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Graduate Student Association, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Statistics Department (Executive Head) II, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Fellowships, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Job Opportunities, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Draft Information, 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Summer Quarter (1969) (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Secret (?) Salaries (The Underground Press), 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Chairman, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Student Support, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Graduate Students Association, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Strike, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Fellowships, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Job Opportunities, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Summer Quarter, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Tenure Faculty Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Chairman, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Job Opportunities, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Tenure Faculty, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Student Support, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Job Classification, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Indirect Costs and Expenditures, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Bachetti Numbers, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Graduate Students Association, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Summer Quarter, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Chairman, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Visitors, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Graduate Students, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Teaching Schedules, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Electronic Desk Calculators, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Summer Quarter 1972 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- PHS Training Grant, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- NIH Site Visit/ Grant Renewal, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- NIH Travel Grant Renewal, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- NIH Travel Grant Budget, 1972-1978 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- NIH Training - Budget Statements and Correspondence, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- NIH Training Grant Application, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Applied Statistics 233A - Applied Statistics (Autumn 1985) I (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Applied Statistics 233A - Applied Statistics (Autumn 1985) II (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Applied Statistics 233B - Applied Statistics (Winter 1984) I (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Applied Statistics 233B - Applied Statistics (Winter 1984) II (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Applied Statistics 233A - Applied Statistics (Autumn 1983) I (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Applied Statistics 233A - Applied Statistics (Autumn 1983) II (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Applied Statistics 233A,B,C - Applied Statistics (Autumn 1976-1977) I (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Applied Statistics 233A,B,C - Applied Statistics (Autumn 1976-1977) II (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Applied Statistics 233A,B,C - Applied Statistics (Autumn 1976-1977) III (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Applied Statistics 233A,B,C - Applied Statistics (Autumn 1976-1977) IV (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Statistics 222 - Analysis of Variance II - Notebook 1, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Statistics 222 - Analysis of Variance II - Notebook 2, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Statistics 221 - Analysis of Variance I, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Statistics 221 - Analysis of Variance II, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Analysis of Variance I, 1966-1967 (Box 35, Folder 5)